Guide to the Center for American Music Photos CAM.PHOTOS.2017
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Memorial booklet for Madge Rowan Frost, 1925 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 454)
  - Memorial booklet for Madge Rowan Frost: Cover page reading "In Memory of Madge Rowan Frost, mistress of My Old Kentucky Home from her Sister Maude Rowan Starr", 1925 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 454.01)
  - Memorial booklet for Madge Rowan Frost: Madge Rowan Frost's Obituary, 1925 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 454.02)
  - Memorial booklet for Madge Rowan Frost: Mrs. Madge Rowan Frost lying in State at My Old Kentucky Home, 1925 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 454.03)
  - Memorial booklet for Madge Rowan Frost: Services at the Old Church in Bardstown, KY, 1925 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 454.04)
  - Memorial booklet for Madge Rowan Frost: At the burial, 1925 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 454.05)
  - Memorial booklet for Madge Rowan Frost: At the grave the last scene, 1925 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 454.06)
  - Memorial booklet for Madge Rowan Frost: Maude Rowan Frost's gravestone, 1925 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 454.07)
- Fletcher Hodges Jr. with Robert H. Caffee looking at The Songs of Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 455)
- Fletcher Hodges Jr. with Robert H. Caffee. Caffee holding The Songs of Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 456)
- Fletcher Hodges Jr., 1945 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 457)
- Louis P. Kleber, nephew of Henry Kleber. Louis Kleber died July 1941 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 458)
- Mrs. Jessie Welch Rose, holding her grandson, Bruce Alexander Rose (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 459)
- Mrs. Andrew L. Robinson (Susan E. Pentland) taken just before her death, 1916 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 460)
- Rededication and patriotic program at Lawrenceville Burial Grounds Arsenal 897, May 15, 1955 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 461)
- Jessie Rose Welsh and Maybelle Welsh, 1899 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 462)
  - Jessie and Maybelle Welsh, 1899 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 462.01)
  - Jessie and Maybelle Welsh colorized (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 462.02)
- Burial photo at grave of Madge Rowan, Bardstown, KY, 1925 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 463)
- McCormick Family Stephen Foster Musicale, 1960 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 464)
  - McCormick Family Stephen Foster Musicale: John, Veronica, and James McCormack singing a trio arrangement of "Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming", March 19, 1960 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 464.01)
  - McCormick Family Stephen Foster Musicale: John McCormick singing "Old Dog Tray", March 19, 1960 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 464.02)
  - McCormick Family Stephen Foster Musicale: Veronica and James McCormick as Jean and William Barclay Foster, Jr., singing "Old Folks at Home" and "Old Black Joe", March 19, 1960 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 464.03)
  - McCormick Family Stephen Foster Musicale: Michael McCormick as a nephew of Stephen (four years old) singing "Nelly Bly", March 19, 1960 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 464.04)
  - McCormick Family Stephen Foster Musicale: Alice McCormick (8 years old) as Stephen's daughter Marion singing "Fairy Belle", March 19, 1960 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 464.05)
  - McCormick Family Stephen Foster Musicale: Alice (8 years old) and Francis McCormick (as Henry Foster) age ten years old doing the Schottische, March 19, 1960 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 464.06)
  - McCormick Family Stephen Foster Musicale: John McCormick as Stephen Foster (sixteen years old) singing "Oh Susanna" and "Camptown Races" for a Stephen Foster Musical benefit for the El Portal Woman's Club, March 19, 1960 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 464.07)
  - McCormick Family Stephen Foster Musicale: John and Cecilia McCormick as Stephen and Ann Eliza Foster doing the minuet. Master of Ceremonies Edward McCormick as Dunning Foster seated, March 19, 1960 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 464.08)
  - McCormick Family Stephen Foster Musicale: Louise and Cecila McCormick as Henrietta and Ann Eliza Foster singing "Open Thy Lattice Love", March 19, 1960 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 469.09)
  - McCormick Family Stephen Foster Musicale: Veronica McCormick, the 1959 Jeanie of White Springs, FL, singing "Jeanie with the Light Brown Hair" and "Beautiful Dreamer", March 19, 1960 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 464.1)
- Stephen Foster Singers, Manual Training High School, Peoria, IL (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 465)
- Leona Sellin (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 467)
  - Leona Sellin seated with her shoes off in front of a typewriter (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 466.01)
  - Leonora G. Baird seated on the steps of the Cathedral of Learning (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 466.02)
  - Leona G. Sellin seated on the steps of the Cathedral of Learning (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 466.03)
  - Virginia Frye and Regina D. Leonardo in front of the Cathedral of Learning (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 466.04)
  - Leona G. Sellin and Virginia Miller in front of the Cathedral of Learning (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 466.05)
  - Virginia Frye seated on the steps of the Cathedral of Learning (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 466.06)
- Stephen Foster Statue, 1990 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 467)
  - Stephen Foster Statue, Schenley Park, 1990 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 467.01)
  - Stephen Foster Statue, Schenley Park, 1990 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 467.02)
  - Stephen Foster Statue, Schenley Park, 1990 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 467.03)
  - Stephen Foster Statue, Schenley Park, 1990 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 467.04)
- Stephen C. Foster Memorial Home in Pittsburgh, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 468)
- Original black and white copy of painting of Federal Hill, KY, by Bauscher, 1927 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 469)
- Original watercolor of doorway, Federal Hill, KY, by Pennell, M.H., 1934 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 470)
- Photo of the University of Pittsburgh Chancellor John G. Bowman in 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 471)
- Howard Chandler Christy and Fletcher Hodges with Christy's painting in White Springs (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 472)
- Souvenir photos from Edison Institute, 1931 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 473)
  - At Greenfield Village, Dearborn MI, at dedication of the Foster House, 1931 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 473.01)
  - E.B. Lee and [?] Herndon at dedication of Stephen Foster House, Dearborn, MI, 1931 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 473.02)
- Senorita Elena Oritz DeZevallos holding a ukulele singing "My Old Kentucky Home" (see Foster Hall Bulletin, no. 11, p. 10) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 474)
- Two young men at three Foster sites, 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 475)
  - Two young men standing on the steps of the Foster Memorial Home, 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 475.01)
  - Two young men at Foster's Grave, 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 475.02)
  - Two young men at the Foster statue in Highland Park, 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 475.03)
- Luis Guzman (arranged Stephen Foster Melodies for Marine Band) with Josiah Kirby and Mrs. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 476)
- Meredith Nicholson (an Indiana writer and minister to Paraguay) with Mr. and Mrs. George Butler. See, no. 11, p. 10) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 477)
- Struthers Family graves (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 478)
  - Struthers family monument showing information for John Struthers and Mary Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 478.01)
  - Struthers family monument showing information for Ebeneezer and Thomas (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 478.02)
  - Struthers family monument showing information for Drusilla and Emma and Matilda (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 478.03)
  - Struthers Family monument showing information for Sam McBride, Alexander, and Mary (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 478.04)
  - Cement grave marker (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 478.05)
- David Bispham and Fannie Bloomfield-Zeisler (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 479)
- Negative image of E.P. Christy (small version of no. 13063 in black volumes) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 480)
- Das Bostoner Kneisel - Quartet (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 481)
- Negative image of Stephen Collins Foster sketch (Small version of no. 14346 in black volumes) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 482)
- W.C. Handy, father of American Blues and first black independent music publisher - visited the Foster Memorial, Pittsburgh, in 1942. Signed "To Fletcher Hodges Jr. with sincere appreciation W.C. Handy, 5-20-42", May 20, 1942 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 483)
- Victor Herbert (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 484)
- Henry L. Higginson (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 485)
- Washington Irving (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 486)
- Negative image of Nord-amerikanischer Saengerbund, Saengerfest (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 487)
- Negative images of Ole Bull's Gaspar di Salo and a Nicholas Amati (violins) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 488)
- Negative image of "Pittsburgh and Allegheny" - print from engraving (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 489)
- Unidentified portraits (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 490)
  - Portrait of unidentified woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 490.01)
  - Portrait of unidentified man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 490.02)
- John K. Paine (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 491)
- The Late T.D. Rice, from a Photograph in G.M. Howard's Theatrical Portrait Gallery (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 492)
- Edgar Stillman-Kelley (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 493)
- Frank Van Der Stucken (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 494)
- Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 495)
  Photographed for the Foster Hall Collection in summer, 1945. Original is in the library of the Indiana Historical Society.
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: cover page, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.01)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 250-251, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.02)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 252-253, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.03)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 254-255, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.04)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 256-257, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.05)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 258-259, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.06)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 260-261, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.07)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 262-263, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.08)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 264-265, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.09)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 266-267, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.1)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 268-269, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.11)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 270-271, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.12)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 272-273, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.13)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 274-275, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.14)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: pages 276-277, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.15)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: photos 278 and 279, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.16)
  - Negative photostat of Hudson and Mississippi: page 280, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 495.17)
- Swanee River off right side of boat (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 496)
- Scenes on the Peedee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 497)
  - Scenes on the Pee Dee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 497.01)
  - Scenes on the Pee Dee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 497.02)
  - Scenes on the Pee Dee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 497.03)
  - Scenes on the Pee Dee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 497.04)
  - Scenes on the Pee Dee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 497.05)
- Small photo of the Swanee River behind billboard of "Jungle Drive" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 498)
- Small photo of Swanee River scene. Ellaville, FL, March 25, 1935 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 499)
- Suwanee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 500)
  - Suwanee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Item 500.01)
  - Suwanee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 500.02)
- Photo of Swanee River, J.K. Lilly and guests boating on the Swanee river (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 501)
- Photo of scene along the Swanee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 502)
- Old Gate at Lawrenceville Arsenal, April 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 503)
  - Old Gate at Arsenal located on Butler Street across from Arsenal School, April 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 503.01)
  - The Old Arsenal Gate, Lawrenceville, April 12, 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 503.02)
- Photostats of genealogy of Foster family, June 1942 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 505)
  - First page of a form describing family history for Robert Verrell Foster of Lebanon, TN (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 505.01)
  - Second page of family history for Robert Verrell Foster of Lebanon, TN (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 505.02)
  - Third page of a form family history for Robert Verrell Foster of Lebanon, TN (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 505.03)
- East Common, Pittsburgh, near the site of Foster's Home, April 12, 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 506)
  - View across East common from site of Foster home -- largest building present Elk's club, approximate site of Andrew Robinson's house, April 12, 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 506.01)
  - First M.P. Church East Common Allegheny, April 12, 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 506.02)
  - From site of Foster home, East Common, Allegheny, looking toward Pittsburgh, April 12, 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 506.03)
  - Entrance to what was probably Gay Alley from East Common, Allegheny, April 12, 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 506.04)
  - Looking North from site of Foster home on East Commons, Allegheny, April 12, 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 506.05)
  - Allegheny, corner of what was probably Gay Alley and East Common. House marked was probably site of Foster home 1837-9 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 506.06)
- Small photo of Greenbark High School, Pocahontas Co., W. VA. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 507)
- Jefferson College (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 508)
  - Drawing of Jefferson College at Canonsburg, 1840 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 508.01)
  - Photo of Jefferson College at Canonsburg (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 508.02)
- Maps of Lawrenceville (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 509)
  - Lawrenceville section of map of Pittsburgh, published by Robert Patterson Pittsburgh, December 24, 1816 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 509.01)
  - Lawrenceville section of map of Pittsburgh published by Robert Patterson, December 24, 1816 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 509.02)
  - The Outlots 1815-1816, 1885 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 509.03)
  - A portion of Lawrenceville, 1900 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 509.04)
- Lithograph "View of Nashville" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 510)
- Photo of Pittsburgh house at the fork of the road before its removal (house that Henry Ford bought), 1934 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 511)
- Cleveland and Pittsburgh Railroad (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 512)
  - Cleveland and Pittsburgh Railroad map with mileages from Philadelphia (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 512.01)
  - Railroad Map of U.S. from Minnesota to Maine (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 512.02)
- Silhouette - study of Stephen Collins Foster, William B. Foster and Eliza Foster, framed on wall (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 513)
- The Suwanee River, seen from the Hillman Bridge on U.S. route 90, between Tallahassee and Jacksonville, FL, midway between Madison and Live Oak, near Ellaville, FL, 1936 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 514)
- Kathy Haines, Deane Root, and Kanako Tateishi in the Foster reading room, 2002 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 515)
- Dennis Kobray, performer, researching in the Foster reading room, 2003 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 516)
- Stephen Foster Memorial at Calvary, Episcopal Church in Fletcher, North Carolina (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 517)
- Color Postcard of Daniel Decatur Emmett and his residence (author of "Dixie") (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 518)
- Deane Root and Mrs. Teruko Shiono placing a wreath at Foster's gravesite in Allegheny Cemetery, January 13, 2004 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 519)
- Hillman Bridge over the Swanee River on U.S. Route 90 between Tallahassee and Jacksonville, 1936 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 520)
- Aerial view of Foster Memorial under construction with crowd present for cornerstone placement ceremony, June 3, 1934 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 521)
- Ground breaking ceremony for Foster Memorial at the University of Pittsburgh. Mrs. Will Earhart turns the first spade full of earth, January 13, 1935, the 71st anniversary of Foster's death, while his granddaughter (Jessie Welch Rose, with the dash of white in her hat) looks on (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 522)
- Sketch of the Foster Memorial with the Cathedral of Learning and Heinz Memorial Chapel in the background (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 523)
- Stephen Foster Memorial with man in the foreground, August 13, 1941 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 524)
- The Stephen Foster Memorial from Forbes Avenue (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 525)
- Corridor into the Foster museum showing stained glass windows (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 526)
- Side view of the Stephen Foster Memorial (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 527)
- The house located at 3600 Penn Avenue, two views (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 529)
  - Vertical shot of the house at 3600 Penn Avenue with iron gate (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 529.01)
  - Horizontal shot of the house at 3600 Penn Avenue (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 529.02)
- First floor living room the Foster Memorial Home (3600 Penn Avenue) showing Foster Display, October 1, 1927 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 530)
- Deane Root at Foster's gravesite with wreaths, January 12, 1996 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 531)
- Bach-Handel Society of Tokyo, 1951 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 532)
  - Bach Handel Society of Tokyo, 1951 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 532.01)
  - Bach Handel Society of Tokyo, 1951 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 532.02)
- Tear sheet from Evelyn Foster Morneweck's includes three different photos, 00190, 00203, and 00533 on a single page (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 534)
- Tear sheet from Evelyn Foster Morneweck's showing a sketch of the Warren, Ohio, home of Stephen Foster with caption, 1860 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 535)
- Tearsheet from showing friends of Morrison and Stephen Foster: Clement L. Vallandigham; Charles W. Couldock and his daughter Eliza; Matthew I. Stewart of Allegheny (and owner of Old Dog Tray) with caption (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 536)
- Morrison Foster's daughter Evelyn, 1880 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 537)
- Evelyn Foster Morneweck, 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 538)
- Foster's siblings (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 539)
  - Tearsheet of Evelyn Foster Morneweck's showing Stephen's siblings Henry, Morrison, Ann Eliza and Henrietta with caption (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 539.01)
  - Cropped photo of Stephen's siblings Henry, Morrison, Ann Eliza and Henrietta (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 539.02)
- Mrs. Jessie Welsh Rose (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 540)
- unidentified young woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 540.14)
- Tearsheet from featuring outlots of Lawrenceville (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 541)
- Tearsheet from depicting Robert McGowin's 1852 map of Pittsburgh (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 542)
- Tear sheet from featuring the Robert Bell plan of the Malcolm Leech property, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 543)
- Tear sheet from featuring an article from The Pittsburgh Sun about the birthplace of Stephen Foster controversy, February 17, 1927 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 544)
- Tear sheet from Evelyn Foster Morneweck's The Chronicles of Stephen Foster's Family showing a comparison between the Foster home drawn by Miller and the house purchased by Henry Ford (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 545)
- Tear sheet from Evelyn Foster Morneweck's The Chronicles of Stephen Foster's Family showing the Rowan Family mansion and an inset image of Judge Rowan (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 546)
- Tear sheet from Evelyn Foster Morneweck's The Chronicles of Stephen Foster's Family showing map of the New York and Erie Railroad (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 547)
- Tear sheet from Evelyn Foster Morneweck's The Chronicles of Stephen Foster's Family showing the Maria Bach Waltz (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 548)
- Tear sheet from Evelyn Foster Morneweck's The Chronicles of Stephen Foster's Family showing Cincinnati in 1846 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 549)
- Tear sheet from Evelyn Foster Morneweck's The Chronicles of Stephen Foster's Family showing Cincinnati in the 1850s (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 550)
- Tear sheet from Evelyn Foster Morneweck's The Chronicles of Stephen Foster's Family showing Julia Nancy Murray's portrait, to whom Foster dedicated "Wilt Thou Be Gone, Love", 1849 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 551)
- Henrietta Crosman in costume (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 552)
- Miller's painting of The White Cottage (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 553)
- Preliminary design of Stephen Foster Memorial (not the final design) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 554)
- Josiah Lilly seated next to a grandfather clock (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 555)
- "Open Thy Lattice Love", 1844 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 556)
  - Published score of "Open Thy Lattice Love," page 1, 1844 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 556.01)
  - Published score of "Open Thy Lattice Love," page 2, 1944 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 556.02)
- Newsprint image of Charlotte Tompkins of Allegheny (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 557)
- William B. Foster (son of Morrison Foster, nephew of Stephen) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 558)
  - William B. Foster (son of Morrison Foster, nephew of Stephen): William B. Foster in France, reprinted on postcards, 1918 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 558.01)
  - William B. Foster (son of Morrison Foster, nephew of Stephen):William B. Foster taken in France, August 1818 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 558.02)
  - William B. Foster (son of Morrison Foster, nephew of Stephen):William B. Foster in France, 1917 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 558.03)
  - William B. Foster (son of Morrison Foster, nephew of Stephen):William B. Foster, 1917 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 558.04)
  - William B. Foster (son of Morrison Foster, nephew of Stephen):William B. Foster and Betty Roberts a Camp Oakmont[?], 1917 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 558.05)
  - William B. Foster (son of Morrison Foster, nephew of Stephen):William B. Foster as a toddler (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 558.06)